체코 공화국
2001년
(brakes hiss)
(car approaching)
(silenced gunshot)
(knocking)
Martin: General Arsanov,
it's Dmitry Petrovich.
알사노브 장군
드미트리요
(gun clicks)
What's happening?
아까 무슨 일이었지?
American cop tried to stop truck
a few kilometers back.
몇 마일 전에 미국 경찰 놈이
트럭을 멈추게 했었소
He shot Musa, but Musa was brave,
그 자식이 무사를 쐈지만
용감하게 전사했소
kept driving to protect you.
당신을 보호하려고
트럭을 멈추지 않았지
- So why do we stop?
- Cop shot tires.
- 근데 지금 왜 멈춘거지?
- 경찰이 따라 붙었소
Musa stopped to fix, but he was too hurt.
타이어를 교체하려고 했는데
무사는 큰 부상을 당했고
He's dead.
죽었소
And you are not hurt at all, yeah?
자네는 다친데가 전혀 없고?
I stay behind, shoot cop.
뒤에서 경찰을 쐈소
Take his car, catch up to you.
그 자식 차를 타고
당신을 따라 온거요
Maybe you are lying.
거짓말일 수도 있지
It's business, General.
이건 사업일 뿐이오, 장군
Your cargo.
당신 물건을 옮기지 못하면
나도 돈을 못받겠지
I don't deliver, I don't get paid.
Come on, let's go.
어서 출발하지
Only room for one in trunk.
트렁크에 한 사람만 탈 수 있소
Come.
어서
Or I leave you here for police to find you.
아니면 경찰한테 잡히게
그냥 두고 가겠소
(quietly): I see sign for petrol station,
주유소 간판을 봤소
maybe two kilometer.
2킬로 정도 떨어진 곳에서
Someone will meet you there.
누군가 그곳에 당신을 만나러 갈거요
(engine starts)
(tires screech)
It's all gone to hell.
상황이 완전 꼬였어요
Terrence: The package?
물건은?
I've got it, but you've
got a mess to clean up.
데리고 있어요
이쪽 정리 좀 해줘요
What happened?
무슨 일인가?
Ballard got in the way.
발러드가 또 방해해서
I shot him.
총을 쐈어요
Christ.
제기랄
- Is he dead?
- I don't know.
- 죽은거야?
- 나도 몰라요
But you got to send Steve to
pick up Ilyana and the girl.
그리고 일리아나랑 딸을 데리러
스티브를 보내요
Petrol station three kilometers
west of Brno on Highway 13.
13번 고속도록에서 브르노 서쪽 방향으로
3 킬로미터 떨어진 주유소에 있을거예요
You just shot an American federal agent.
자넨 미연방 요원을 쏜거야
Everyone in Prague is looking for you.
프라하에 있는 모든 사람이
자넬 찾을거라고
Complete your mission, deliver the package,
미션을 완료하고 물건을 옮긴 후
and get yourself to the bloody exfil site.
빌어먹을 그곳에서 당장 빠져나와
No, I'm not going anywhere
till I know you have the girls.
아뇨, 당신이 일리아나와 딸을 데려가기 전까지
아무데도 가지 않을 거예요
Bring them to the safe
house. I'll meet you there.
안전한 곳으로 데려가고
거기서 만나죠
Curtis!
커티스!
Oh, my God.
세상에
Dmitry...
드미트리가...
took my car.
내 차를 가져갔어
It's all right.
걱정마
(groans)
당장 구급차 보내
Curtis, stay with me.
커티스, 조금만 참아
Are you with me?
알았지?
You're going to be okay.
괜찮을거야
(guns clicking)
이게 무슨 짓이야?
이자는 살려줘
(engines starting, doors closing)
Synced & Corrected by - robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
번역: 레전드
www.bunyuc.com
www.tailorcontents.com
프라하
현재
Gabi: Tamir Zakayev obtained
타미르 자카에브가
work visas for three Russian men.
여기 세명의 러시아인의 비자를 받았습니다
We talked to two of
them, both from Chechnya.
이 중 체첸니아에서 온
두명은 조사했고
They were clean.
아무 이상 없었죠
But the third guy, Vahka Baiev,
세번째 남자, 바카 바에브는
is still at large.
아직까지 확인되지 않고 있습니다
They all worked at the Rezlev
이들 모두 리베르에 있는
air conditioning factory in Liber.
레즈레브 에어컨 생산 공장에서 일했고
Vahka's coworkers say he
didn't speak a word of Russian
동료들의 증언에 따르면 이자는 러시아나
체첸말을 할줄 모른다고 합니다
or Chechen.
Six weeks after he
started to work, he quit.
일을 시작한지 6주 후에
그만둔 뒤로
No one's seen him since.
이자를 본 사람이 없습니다
Guy doesn't look Russian or Chechen.
저 남자는 러시아나 체첸 사람으로는 안보이는군요
He looks Middle Eastern.
중동쪽 사람 같은데
I'll share the photo with our
Egyptian and Saudi liaisons,
저 사진을 이집트와 사우디쪽 담당자한테
보내도록 하지요
see if anyone knows him.
알아보는 사람이 있는지 찾아봐야겠어요
그럼 시작하죠
여기서 뭐하는거야?
너무 열심히 일하길래
커피가 필요할 것 같아서
뭔가 찾았어?
집에 가있어, 크리스토프
Gabi...
가비...
난 이번일과 관련없어, 알았어?
체첸니아
현재
Malika: You must eat, Katya.
좀 먹어, 카트야
You haven't touched anything for days.
며칠동안 아무것도 안먹었잖니
I'd rather starve to death
than marry that old man.
저 늙은이랑 결혼할 바에야
굶어죽는게 나아요
How can you let this happen?
어떻게 그냥 내버려둘수 있죠?
I'm going to tell you a secret.
너한테 한가지 비밀을 말해주마
You will not have to marry him.
저 사람과 결혼하지 않을거야
What do you mean?
무슨 말이죠?
Your Uncle Tamir
네 삼촌은
will come here from Prague,
프라하에서 여기로 오겠지만
but the president will not return.
대통령은 다시 돌아오지 못할거야
Ever.
절대
프라하
현재
♪
(tires screech)
예정대로
(vibrates)
On schedule. Track the signal.
예정대로라..
위치 추적해
- On it.
- Could be Beslan.
- 알겠습니다
- 베슬란일거야
Could be anyone.
다른 사람일 수도 있죠
Whoever it is doesn't know Tamir is dead.
그게 누구든지 아직 타미르가
죽은걸 모른다는거지
Got him.
찾았습니다
On the move near Republic Square.
공화국 광장 근처에서 이동 중 입니다
Call a police unit to meet us there.
그쪽으로 오라고 경찰에 알려
(woman speaks Czech over phone)
(speaks Czech)
(trolley bell dinging)
(tires screeching)
(electronic tone chimes)
안타요?
We're looking for a white
male, 20s, with a beard.
20대, 수염을 기른
백인 남자를 찾고 있다
What do you got?
뭐 찾은거 없어?
(trolley bell dinging)
He's heading south, moving pretty fast.
남쪽으로 빠르게 이동 중이에요
- Could be driving.
- He's heading south.
- 차로 움직이는 것 같아요
- 남쪽으로 이동 중이래요
The tram. The tram!
전차!
저 전차야!
- Stop it!
- (speaking Czech)
저거 세워!
(tires screech)
(shouting in Czech)
Call the phone.
전화해봐
(cell phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
체코 공화국
2001년
혈압이 80/52로 떨어지고 있어요
용의자가 초록색 스코다를 훔쳐 달아났어
찾아내
(siren wailing)
Come.
나오세요
Ilyana: We were taken from our home
어떤 남자가 저희를 집으로 데리고 가려고 했어요
by that man.
He had gun.
총을 가지고 있었죠
DALEK: How did you get away from him?
어떻게 도망친거죠?
Someone open truck.
누군가 트럭문을 열었어요
There was yelling and shooting.
싸우는 소리와 총소리가 들렸죠
I'm afraid, so I keep Katya inside with me.
너무 무서워서, 딸을 데리고 안에 숨어있었어요
When it's quiet again, we come out.
그리고 다시 조용해졌을때
빠져나왔죠
I see that man is dead, so we run.
저 남자가 죽은 걸 알고
바로 도망쳤어요
This is horrible night.
너무 끔찍했어요
Can someone take us home please?
집에 데려다 줄수 있나요?
(speaks Czech)
We have a problem.
문제가 생겼어요
We'll need you to come to the
police station in the morning
내일 아침에 경찰서로 와주셔야겠어요
to give a full statement.
서류를 작성해야 되서요
Of course.
물론이죠
(kisses)
Tamir: Ilyana.
일리아나
How are you here?
어떻게 여기 있는거예요?
Wh... where's General Arsanov?
아..아, 알사노브 장군은?
How dare you try to ship me
to Chechnya like piece of meat.
어떻게 감히 날 물건마냥
체첸니아로 보내려고 한거야?
General order it.
장군 명령이었어요
I was carrying out his wishes.
그분이 원하는걸 한 것 뿐이에요
Doku would have wanted it.
형이 원하는 것이기도 했죠
Doku is dead.
도쿠는 죽었어
This house belongs to me now.
이 집은 이제 내 소유야
I want you out by morning.
아침에 나가주면 좋겠어
Great. Thanks.
잘했네, 고맙군
- (elevator bell dings)
- Fantastic. Okay.
잘됐어, 알았네
The FBI agent's in critical condition.
FBI 요원이 위독한 상태라는군
Where are Ilyana and Katya?
일리아나랑 카트야는요?
Czech police found them
before Steve got there.
스티브가 가기전에
체코 경찰이 먼저 발견했네
Detective interviewed
them; they're at home.
형사가 간단하게 면담을 하고
집으로 보냈다네
I'm gonna get them.
데리러 가야겠어요
How?
어떻게?
Dmitry!
드미트리!
What happened? Ilyana will tell me nothing.
무슨 일이야?
일리아나는 아무말도 안해
We were ambushed, by Russians.
매복을 당했어, 러시아 놈들한테
Why did you make me transport girls?
왜 나한테 여자를 옮기게 한거야?
Screwed up everything.
모든게 틀었어
Crazy FBI guy looking for them.
미친 FBI 남자가 놈들을 쫒고 있었고
I had to shoot him.
난 그자를 쏠 수밖에 없었다고
I am in big trouble.
상황이 안좋아
I have to leave Prague.
프라하를 떠나야겠어
Now.
지금 당장
I need money.
돈이 필요해
My trucks,
내 트럭이랑
my club... they are yours.
내 클럽...모두 이제 자네거야
Buy me out. I give you good price,
자네가 사
가격은 잘 쳐줄게
but I need cash now.
대신 당장 현금이 필요해
Let me see how much I have in the safe.
지금 얼마나 있는지 확인해볼게
(door opens, closes)
Go to this address.
이 주소로
6:00 this morning.
아침 6시까지 가시오
슬로바키아/우크라이나 경계
2001년
넌 누구야?
우리가 누군지 알텐데, 장군
체첸니아에서 너무 많이 피를 뿌렸지
체첸 사람들...
러시아 사람들 피...
러시아는 체첸이 평화롭길 바라네
사람들한테 존경을 받는 사람의 지배 아래
바로 영웅 말일세
그 사람의 말에 귀를 귀울리고
함께 일을 해나갈 그런 사람
우리는 그런 사람한테 힘을 줄수 있지
그를 지원하고
보호하고
대신에...
우리에게 협력하길 바라네
(sighs)
난 당신들 꼭두각시가 아냐
자네는 우리가 주는걸 받고
체첸을 통치할 수 있네
아니면...
그럼...
어떻게 하겠나, 장군?
프라하
현재
Welcome to Prague, Mr. President.
프라하에 온걸 환영합니다
대통령 각하
I am honored to be at this crucial summit.
이런 중대한 회담에 오게 되서 영광이오
The war against terror is a global fight.
테러에 대응하는건 전세계적인 전쟁이요
(reporters murmuring)
Egyptian intelligence just I.D.'d our man.
이집트 요원이 그 남자의 신원을 밝혀냈어요
Real name is Omar Wasem.
진짜 이름은 오마르 와셈
He's a bloody bomb maker.
망할 폭탄 제조자지
Who works at an air-conditioning factory
그 에어컨 생산 공장에서 생산된 물건들이
that ships units all over Prague.
프라하 전역에 공급됐어요
He could've planted
explosives in any of them.
거기에 폭탄을 심어놨을 거예요
(cash register clicking)
(dialing)
(line ringing)
Malika: Hello?
여보세요?
I think Tamir is dead.
타미르가 죽은것 같아요
What happened?
무슨 일이야?
Tamir found out who killed his brother.
삼촌 형을 죽인 놈을 찾았어요
Russian pig called Dmitry.
드미트리라는 러시아 새끼죠
So Tamir went to kill him.
삼촌이 그자를 죽이러 갔는데
But Dmitry came after me.
드미트리가 제 뒤를 쫓고 있어요
The only way Dmitry is
alive is if he killed Tamir.
드미트리가 살아있다는건
그자식이 삼촌을 죽인거예요
My God.
세상에
What do we do?
이제 어쩌죠?
어떻게 하냐고요?
President Arsanov wishes
to marry your cousin Katya.
알사노브 대통령이 네 사촌 카트야랑
결혼하려고해
Katya?
카트야?
Why?
왜요?
He will take a second wife.
두번째 아내로 삼으려고
Like the Prophet.
선지자처럼
If Tamir isn't here to protect us,
타미르가 우릴 보호하지 못하면
this will keep us safe.
우린 얌전히 있어야 돼
Make us important people in Chechnya.
체첸니아에서 우리를 필요로 하게
만드는 수밖에 없어
Yes, but Arsanov won't be...
알아요, 하지만 알사노브는...
Beslan.
베슬란
Listen to me.
내 말 잘들어
You must keep the president alive.
대통령이 죽게 내버려둬선 안돼
Those men... they are already
on their way to kill him.
그 사람들은...이미 암살계획을
실행에 옮기고 있다고요
You must stop them.
네가 못하게 막아
How?
어떻게요?
I need to speak someone in charge.
담당자와 얘기하러 왔어요
MAN: Yes? (speaks Czech)
네?
I have information
체첸니아 대통령을 암살하려는
about a plot to kill the
president of Chechnya.
정보를 가지고 있어요
A list of all the air-conditioning units
그 이집트 사람이 작업했을 걸로
the Egyptian may have worked on.
추정되는 에어컨 목록이에요
Christ, that's huge.
세상에, 너무 많아
They ship 50 units per week.
일주일에 50개는 운반했어요
(phone ringing)
Miskova.
미스코바입니다
곧 그리로 가죠
Okay, thank you.
알겠어요
That was Gabi's office.
가비 사무실이에요
Beslan's turned himself in.
베슬란이 자수했어요
He can tell us where Kate is.
그자식이 케이트가 어딨는지 말할거요
Get me in to see him.
내가 그자를 보러 가겠소
Well, you're gonna have to wait your turn.
당신 차례를 기다려요
Simon and Gabi are taking a crack at him.
사이먼과 가비가 먼저 심문할거니까
Well, call them back, Nina.
그럼 다시 전화해요, 니나
Tell them to ask him about Kate.
케이트에 대해 물어보라고 전해요
Martin, they will.
마틴, 그 사람들이 알아서 할거예요
But apparently, he's got a different story
아무래도 그자가 먼저 얘기하는건
he wants to tell first.
다른 것과 관련된 것 같아요
Beslan: My uncle Tamir asked me
내 삼촌, 타미르가
to help two men, Chechens,
두명의 체첸 사라을 도와달라고 했어요
get into the country.
이 나라로 들어올 수 있게요
They are workers, he tells me,
저한테는 그냥 노동자라고 했어요
coming to Prague to get jobs.
프라하에 일자리를 구하러 온거라고요
I give them passports, that's all.
제가 그들의 여권을 줬죠, 그게 다예요
But then I hear them talking.
하지만 그자들이 말하는걸 들었는데
They say they are here
to kill President Arsanov.
알사노브 대통령을 죽이려고 왔다고 했어요
He's a great man.
대통령은 아주 훌륭한 사람이라서
I knew I had to stop this.
이걸 막아야겠다는 생각이 들었죠
You must warn him.
당신들이 경고해줘야 되요
We thought Tamir was
planning a terror attack.
우리는 타미르가 테러 공격을
꾸민다고 생각했는데
It was actually an assassination.
실제로는 암살 계획이었던 거예요
No, he's trying to get us
아니요, 저자는 지금
to pull security away
from the signing ceremony.
조인식에 보안요원을 더 밀어넣으려고 하는 거예요
We call in the threat,
the police rush there,
위협에 대해 경고하고 경찰을 보내면
and the bomb goes off someplace else.
폭탄은 다른 곳에서 터지겠죠
Maybe.
그럴 수도 있죠
But we still have to notify
Arsanov's security team.
하지만 알사노브 보안팀에 알려야겠어요
Thank you for informing us.
알려줘서 감사합니다
Chechnya is new land of opportunity.
체첸니아는 새로운 기회의 땅입니다
Excuse me, Mr. President.
실례하겠습니다, 대통령 각하
대통령 각하를 노린다는 정보를 받았습니다
안전한 장소로 이동하셔야 될것 같습니다
Excuse me, gentlemen.
실례하죠, 여러분
Simon: I'll let you in on a little secret.
비밀 하나를 알려주지
We've been watching you and Tamir
우리는 너와 타미르르
for the last six months.
지난 6달동안 감시하고 있었어
We know you drove Kate Crawford from Paris.
네가 케이트 크로포드를 파리에서 꺼내온걸 알아
Where is she?
지금 어딨지?
I don't know.
나도 몰라요
You're going to prison, Beslan.
감옥에 가야겠군, 베슬란
President will help me when he knows
내가 대통령의 목숨을 살린걸 안다면
I'm the one who saved his life.
날 도와줄거예요
Whatever Tamir was
planning, you were in on it.
타미르가 뭘 꾸몄던간에
너도 연관되어 있지
We'll make sure Arsanov knows that.
우리가 알사노브에게 확실히 알려줄거야
He's not going to save you.
네가 그를 살린게 아니라
He's going to have you killed.
네가 죽이려 했다고 말야
Gabi: You want to stay alive?
살길 원해?
We need details.
그럼 아는대로 전부 얘기해
Who are these men? What are they planning?
이 남자들이 누구고
뭘 꾸미고 있는거지?
When will it happen?
언제 진행할거고?
Tamir asked me to get hotel room for them.
삼촌 부탁으로 그 사람들 호텔방을 예약했어요
And a vehicle.
차량도요
Well, what kind of vehicle?
어떤거지?
Gabi: This must be some kind of cover.
뭔가 속임수를 쓸거예요
(quietly): For what?
뭘요?
An accident, an emergency.
사고, 비상사태
An ambulance wouldn't be out of place.
구급차 모두 속임수가 될수 있어요
Simon: The bomb maker could cause
폭탄 제조자가
a pretty big emergency, couldn't he?
큰 비상사태를 만들 수 있죠, 안그래요?
So an explosion is
supposed to kill Arsanov.
폭발로 알사노브가 죽을수도 있죠
But if it doesn't...
아니면...
Simon: There are two killers
waiting for him in an ambulance
두명의 암살자가 구급차에서 대기하고 있을거예요
as he evacuates the signing ceremony.
조인식에서 대피시킬때 말이죠
Gabi: And what if the signing
ceremony is the big diversion,
조인식에서 주의를 딴데로 돌리고
and they're going to kill
Arsanov somewhere else?
알사노르를 다른 곳에서 죽이려고 한다면요?
Where, his motorcade?
어디요?
차량 행렬할떄?
Or his hotel.
아니면 호텔에서요
당장 인터콘티넨셜에 연락해서
즉시 대피시키라고 해
(phone beeps)
(crowd screaming)
(tires screeching)
(alarm ringing, people clamoring)
(coughing)
(sirens wailing)
(phone ringing)
What was your security
protocol for exiting the hotel?
호텔을 벗어날 보안 프로토콜이 뭐죠?
Leave through the loading dock.
하역장쪽으로 탈출하는 겁니다
But we are already out.
이미 탈출했고요
Why are you asking?
왜 물으시는 거죠?
Loading dock.
하역장으로 가
(sirens wailing)
어떤 놈이 날 죽이려는지 알아내
(guns clicking)
대통령은 어디에 있어?
(tires screech)
하역장으로 어떻게 가죠?
따라와
(speaking Czech)
Go.
그냥 가세요
Go!
가라고!
Police!
경찰이다!
Hands in the air! Hands in the air!
손 들어!
총을 가지고 있다!
(gunfire continues)
(officers shouting)
(panting)
프라하
2001년
Curtis.
커티스
It's me. I'm here.
나야, 나 여기있어
(weakly): Did you catch him?
그자 잡았어?
Not yet.
아직
But we're looking.
찾고 있어
(groans softly)
My leg is killing me.
다리가 너무 아파
Curtis, the bullet destroyed the bone,
커티스
총알이 뼈를 작살내고
cut through the arteries.
동맥을 끊었어
The doctors had no choice.
의사는 다른 방법이 없었데
They had to remove your leg.
네 다리를 자를 수밖에 없었어
No.
아냐
No, I can feel it.
그럴리 없어, 느껴져
They say it's called phantom pain.
그걸 환상통이라고 부른데
I'm... I'm so sorry.
정말...정말 유감이야
Please leave me alone.
나 혼자 있게 해줘
(elevator bell dings)
상태는 어때?
어떨것 같아요?
괜찮아?
(sighs)
현장에서 찾은거 없나요?
어떤 단서도?
드미트리에 대한 흔적은 없네
근처에서 일리아나와 그녀 딸을 발견했지
(knocking)
I need to talk to Ilyana. Where is she?
일리아나랑 얘기 좀 해야겠어
어딨어?
Mrs. Zakayeva?
자카에바 부인
Dmitry sent me.
드미트리가 보냈어요
Hello, Ilyana.
안녕하신가, 일리아나
Katya.
카트야
I'm a friend of Dmitry's.
난 드미트리 친구 중 한명이고
My name's Terrence.
테렌스라고 하네
He never mentioned you.
당신에 대해 말한 적이 없는데요
I'm based in London.
내가 런던에 기반을 두고 있어서
He's asked me to help get you there safely.
당신을 안전하게 도와달라고 부탁하더군
My company's handling
all of your of travel...
내 회사가 당신들 여행에 관한 모든걸
처리할거네
accommodation, passports.
숙소, 여권
It's all taken care of.
모두 준비됐네
프라하
현재
Simon: You took care of
everything, didn't you?
네가 준비했지, 안그래?
Passports, the guns, the ambulance?
여권, 총, 구급차 모두?
Beslan: No, I told you,
아뇨, 말했잖아요
- not the guns.
- I'm not done here!
- 총은 모른다고요
- 아직 안 끝났어!
- Where's Kate?!
- Easy!
- 케이트 어딨어?!
- 진정해!
Martin: Huh?
Who are you?
넌 누구야?
Tell me where she is, or I
swear by Christ, I'll kill you.
당장 어딨는지 말해
안그러면 맹세코 네놈을 죽여버리겠어
Get him off of me!
이 사람 좀 치워줘요!
Let's go get a cup of coffee.
커피나 한잔 하러 가지
(panting)
Nobody gives a shit what happens to you.
네놈한테 무슨짓을 해도 아무도 관심없어
Now tell me where she is.
어딨는지 말해
Chechnya.
체첸니아
At the president's country house.
대통령 별장에 있어
But you'll never get her.
절대 못 데리고 올거야
She's going to marry the president.
대통령이랑 결혼할거거든
체첸니아
현재
(woman speaking Russian over TV)
(women murmuring)
What?
네?
What are they saying?
뭐라고 하는 거예요?
Someone tried to kill the president.
누가 대통령을 죽이려고 했지만
But he survived, praise Allah.
살아남았데, 신이시여
He's coming home.
여기고 오고 있단다
Leaving nine dead and 33 wounded.
9명이 사망하고
33명이 중상을 입었습니다
The cell phone believed to have been used
폭탄을 작동시키는데 사용한 핸드폰은
to detonate the bomb was
found in the gunmen's vehicle,
무장 괴한들 차량에서 발견됐으며
leading authorities to believe
지휘 당국에 따르면
that the two Chechens acted alone.
두명의 체첸인의 소행으로 밝혀졌습니다
프라하
2001년
엘더 핸샌
말일 성도 예수 그리스도 교회
Gabi: Curtis?
커티스?
What are you doing?
뭐하는거야?
Uh...
It's nothing. Just...
아무것도, 그냥...
Who's Hanson?
핸슨이 누구야?
He was my Mormon mission companion
내 모르몬 교회 동반자였어
when I was a kid.
내가 어렸을때
He was murdered.
살해당했지
I'm sorry.
유감이야
It was my fault.
내 잘못이였어
After Hanson died, I made a vow to God
핸슨이 죽고 신에게 맹세했지
to become a cop and get justice.
경찰이 되서 정의를 바로 세우겠다고
Fight the bad guys.
나쁜 놈들과 싸우겠다고
It was a big joke, right?
순 거짓말이지, 안그래?
I think God would understand
if you let Dmitry go.
드미트리를 놓친걸 신이 이해해줄거라 생각해
'Cause if you keep trying to catch him...
왜냐면 그자를 잡으려고 했다가
it's going to kill you.
너가 죽었을거야
And I don't think God would want that.
신이 그걸 원하지는 않았을거야
(women speaking Czech)
(man speaking Czech
over TV, crowd murmuring)
(gasps softly)
워싱턴 D.C
2001년
You need to come home, Agent Ballard.
돌아와야겠네, 발러드 요원
I'm not going anywhere
until I find Petrovich.
페트로비치를 잡기 전까지 돌아가지 않을겁니다
I need more resources, a bigger team...
더 많은 자원과 더 큰 팀을...
Have you been watching the news?
뉴스를 보기는 했나?
Nobody gives a shit about
누구도 러시아 조직 폭력배 따위에
관심이 없네, 커티스
Russian mobsters anymore, Curtis.
(line clicks, dial tone hums)
I brought lunch.
점심 사왔어
An American hamburger place.
미국 햄버거 가게에서
Instead of hospital food.
병원 음식 대신에...
They ordered me back to D.C.
위에서 D.C로 돌아오래
Hmm.
Since when does Agent Curtis Ballard
언제부터 발러드 요원이
follow orders?
명령에 복종했어?
I have a friend who works at Interpol.
인터폴에 친구가 있어
Maybe you could get a job there,
거기서 일할수 있을거야
keep looking for Dmitry.
드미트리를 계속 찾을 수 있고
Why do you keep coming here?
왜 계속 여기에 오는거야?
Bringing me food, trying to cheer me up.
음식을 가져오고 날 격려해주고
I don't need your pity.
난 동정은 필요없어
You really don't get it, do you?
정말 모르는구나, 그렇지?
I don't pity you, Curtis.
널 동정하는게 아냐, 커티스
I like you.
널 좋아해
Marry me, Gabi.
나랑 결혼하자, 가비
What?
뭐?
I can stay here and get a job.
이곳에 머물고 일자리를 구할 수 있어
At Interpol, fine, I don't care.
인터폴도 괜찮아
상관없어
We can start a family.
아이를 가질수도 있지
(chuckles softly)
Curtis, I said I liked you,
I didn't say I'd marry you.
커티스, 널 좋아한다고 했지
너와 결혼하겠다고 말한건 아냐
It's just...
그냥...
I'm not... I'm not the marrying type.
난...결혼이랑 어울리는 체질이 아냐
체첸니아
현재
Kate: You said I wouldn't
have to marry him.
그 사람이랑 결혼할 필요없다고 했잖아요
That I'd never see him again.
다시 볼일 절대 없다고
Things don't always go as planned.
항상 계획대로 되는게 아니란다
Now we move forward.
이제 앞으로 나아가야지
You told me he wasn't coming back.
그 사람이 돌아오지 못할거라고 했잖아요
That means you knew
someone was gonna kill him.
그 말은 누군가 그사람을 죽일거라는걸
알고 있었다는 거죠
Maybe I should tell him that.
제가 그걸 말할 수도 있어요
If you do that,
네가 그렇게 한다면
I will tell him that
when Tamir's plan failed,
난 타미르의 계획이 실패하면
you offered to kill him
on your wedding night.
네가 결혼식 첫날에 죽인다고 했다고 말한거란다
- That's ridiculous.
- Really?
- 말도 안되요
- 그럴까?
Aren't you the terrorist
girl from the Paris attack?
넌 파리에서 테러 공격을 했던 아이잖니?
It will be a beautiful wedding.
아름다운 결혼식이 될거야
프라하
현재
Arsanov's people are denying any
knowledge of Kate's whereabouts.
알사노브쪽에서는 케이트에 대해
부인하고 있어요
He's already in the air,
heading back to Chechnya.
이미 비행기로
체첸니아로 돌아가는 길이죠
CIA could send an extraction team.
CIA에서 구조팀을 보내면 되지 않소
Martin, the U.S. government
is about to sign an agreement
마틴, 미국은 러시아와 전세계 테러조직과
of cooperation on global
terror with the Russians.
관련해서 협력하는데 동의 했어요
(scoffs) You think they're gonna
그런 상황에서
authorize an armed incursion
동맹국 영토에
into the sovereign territory of an ally?
무력 침공이라도 허가해야된다고
생각하는건가요?
So that's it, then?
바로 그거요, 아니면?
After all the promises,
you're just gonna let her rot?
약속을 해놓고선
그냥 이래도 방치하겠단 말이오?
Been going through that material you got us
당신이 타미르 컴퓨터에서
off Tamir's computer.
빼내온 걸 조사해보니
Some interesting stuff.
흥미러운 점을 발견했어요
Money transfers.
자금이 송금됐어요
From a bank in Moscow.
모스코바의 은행에서 말이죠
Encrypted comms from the FSB.
FSB의 암호화된 언어로
Their puppet Arsanov became a loose Cannon,
그들 꼭두각시인 알사노브는
어디로 튈지 모르는 사람이 됐고
so they paid Tamir to take him out,
그래서 타미르에게 그자를 없애라고
돈을 보낸 거예요
pin it on Chechen separatists.
체첸 분리주의자들한테 덮어씌우는 거죠
They even promised him a big position
심지어 새로운 체첸 정부의
in the new Chechen government.
큰 자리 하나를 약속했어요
- Oh.
- Someone who needed
누군가...
체첸니아에 가려는 사람이 있다면
to get into Chechnya might be able
to use that information.
이 정보를 이용할 수 있겠죠
I got to run out for a bit.
전 잠깐 자리를 비울거예요
Cleaning team will be
here in about ten minutes
처리반이 10분 뒤에 여기 올거고
to shred the files.
파일들을 전부 폐기할거예요
Martin: I'm going to Chechnya
내가 체첸니아로 갈거요
to bring Kate home.
케이트를 데리러
Why are you doing this?
대체 왜 그렇게까지 하는거예요?
She's not your daughter.
당신 딸이 아니잖아요
You don't even remember her.
심지어 그 애를 기억도 못하고 있죠
You don't remember any of it.
다른 어느것도 기억을 못하잖아요
I remember little things.
몇가지 기억하는게 있소
Kate on a swing.
그네를 타는 케이트
The feeling of home.
집에서 느낀 감정들
When I'm with her and you...
내가 당신과 당신 딸과 함께 했을때...
I feel it again.
그걸 다시 느끼게 됐소
Ilyana.
일리아나
It's all right.
괜찮아요
I can't be who you want me to be.
당신이 원하는 그런 사람이 될수 없소
I never was.
그런 적도 없었지
Didn't you love me?
날 사랑했었나요?
Very much.
아주 많이
And now?
지금은요?
You have a husband.
당신은 남편이 있잖소
Children.
아이들도..
Go back to London.
런던으로 돌아가서
Be with them.
그 사람들과 함께 보내야겠지
Please bring Kate back to me.
케이트를 꼭 데리고 와줘요
체코 공화국
러시아 대사관
(metal detector beeps)
My name is Martin Odum.
내 이름은 마틴 오덤이요
I worked for British
and American intelligence
수십년 넘게
영국과 미국 정보부에서 일했었소
for more than a decade.
I have top secret information
for your chief of directorate.
당신들 책임자에게 제공할
중요 비밀 정보를 가지고 있소
I'm guessing he'll want to talk to me.
그 사람도 나와 얘기하길 원할거요
I know it looks a little cold,
좀 춥다는건 알지만
but, uh, once we get some furniture in here
여기에 가구를 좀 놓고
and flowers in the window boxes,
it'll be... it'll be quite cozy.
창가에 꽃을 가져다 놓으면...
아늑해질거네
Kate: Dmitry!
드미트리 아저씨!
Hey! (speaks Russian)
(chuckles)
Welcome home.
어서 오시오
(both laugh)
프라하
2001년
Gabi: You're going home?
돌아가게?
I can't stay here, Gabi.
여기에 있을수 없어, 가비
I have to let Petrovich go.
페트로비치는 놓아줘야지
You know, my boss was right.
너도 알잖아
내 보스 말이 맞아
Nobody cares about
Russian mobsters anymore.
러시아 조직 폭력배에 아무도 관심 없지
There's a bigger threat now.
더 큰 위협이 있잖아
I have a duty to my country.
내 나라에서 내 의무를 다해야지
Is this because of duty to your country
정말 그것때문이야?
or because I said I wouldn't get married?
아니면 내가 결혼하지 않는다고 해서 그러는거야?
We're too different, Gabi.
우리는 서로 너무 달라, 가비
(chuckles): Curtis.
커티스
I'll miss my flight.
비행기 놓치겠다
Good-bye, Gabi.
잘있어, 가비
(speaks Czech)
프라하
현재
(door opens, closes)
내 아내...
영웅을 위해
당신이 비자를 받게 한 사람이
호텔 폭발 계획을 세웠어
9명의 무고한 사람이 죽었고
(groans)
날 믿어줘...난 전혀 몰랐다고
이제 어떻게 하려고?
잘거야
체첸니아
현재
♪
프라하
현재
(door opens)
I'm told you have some information
자네가 정보를 가지고 있다고 들었네
you'd like to share with us.
우리한테 알려주겠다던데..
I have proof linking
Russian security services
러시아 비밀 정보부가 이번 알사노브 암살과
to the assassination plot against Arsanov.
관련됐다는 증거를 가지고 있소
These show Tamir Zakayev
여기에 타미르 자카에브가
received multiple payments
from accounts traced to the FSB.
FSB에서 다수의 자금을 받은게 기록되어 있지
One of three copies.
3개의 복사본 중 하나로
Anything happens to me,
press get the other two.
나한테 무슨 일 일어난다면
언론에 퍼질거요
So...
그럼...
what do you want?
원하는게 뭔가?
A girl named Kate Crawford
케이트 크로포드라는 여자애가
is being held against her will by Arsanov.
자신의 의지와 상관없이 알사노브에게
감금되어 있소
I want your people to help me
당신들이 내가 그 애를
get her out of Chechnya,
so I can get her back home.
체첸니아에서 꺼내게 도와주시오
그럼 난 그 애를 대리고 돌아가겠소
You really don't remember me, do you?
자넨 정말 날 기억 못하는군, 안그래?
You and I have a long history together...
자네와 난 아주 긴 시간을 함께 했지
Alexei.
알렉세이
Welcome back, comrade.
돌아온걸 환영하네, 동무
Synced & Corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com